<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Launch X Bit치cora de viaje on Bit치cora de Viaje Jaime Esqueda Velasco</title>
    <link>https://jaimeesqueda.github.io/my_launchx_blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Launch X Bit치cora de viaje on Bit치cora de Viaje Jaime Esqueda Velasco</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jaimeesqueda.github.io/my_launchx_blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My experience at LaunchX to this day</title>
      <link>https://jaimeesqueda.github.io/my_launchx_blog/posts/post_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jaimeesqueda.github.io/my_launchx_blog/posts/post_1/</guid>
      <description>Hello that much pleasure I am Jaime Esqueda and today I am going to tell you about my experience in a great adventure that I had the opportunity to belong. It is a full stack developer course taught by Microsoft experts. That&amp;rsquo;s right, at first it seemed like a dream, since I was just starting my learning curve to this area in a self-taught way and without much success. At the beginning of the induction week, I found it quite interesting how Python looks a lot like other database management systems that I had previously worked on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The culture of a software developer</title>
      <link>https://jaimeesqueda.github.io/my_launchx_blog/posts/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jaimeesqueda.github.io/my_launchx_blog/posts/intro/</guid>
      <description>Hello Everobody there, For me, the culture of a software developer consists of the following values::
 Respect Responsibility Honesty Good communication Proactive attitude Trust  As well as philosophy of life a continuous improvement in its administration and process management, thus improving its discipline for a better result in each project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://jaimeesqueda.github.io/my_launchx_blog/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jaimeesqueda.github.io/my_launchx_blog/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>Who am I Hello, here you are going to read a little about me 游뱔
 Hi I&amp;rsquo;m a statistical industrial engineer and I love programming. I love social events and I am in favor of the environment and new advances or technologies that help improve the environment.
 Interests and hobbies I really like learning new things. I love spirituality and knowing tools that help keep me in an optimal state of consciousness.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
